<?xml version="1.0"?>
<extensions>
	<details>
		<title lang="DE">&lt;span style=&quot;color:red&quot;&gt;Nicht unterstützte Erweiterungen - dies sind Erweiterungen, welche von ihren Autoren nicht mehr unterstützt werden. Sie können Logitech Media Server potentiell schaden! Benutzung auf eigene Verantwortung!&lt;/span&gt;</title>
		<title lang="EN">&lt;span style=&quot;color:red&quot;&gt;Unsupported Plugins - these extensions are NOT supported by their authors any more and can potentially break your Logitech Media Server! Use at your own risk!&lt;/span&gt;</title>
	</details>

	<plugins>
		<plugin name="CustomBrowse" creator="Unsupported" email="" link="http://wiki.slimdevices.com/index.php/Custom_Browse_plugin" maxTarget="*" minTarget="7.4.0" sha="209f65c1fac52a5abac98bd17b04c54c3132f4dc" url="http://downloads.isaksson.info/download/do/downloadapplication?name=slimserver-custombrowse&amp;filename=CustomBrowse-2.15.676.zip" version="2.15.676">
			<changes lang="EN">- Available for free, no longer requires a license
				- Compatible with LMS 7.9
			</changes>
			<desc lang="EN">Makes it possible to customize the structure, contents and sorting of the browse menus on the Squeezebox. A new browse menu is configured as a xml file containing the structure and SQL-statements. Please note that Custom Browse needs a bit more resources than small plugins and might also slow down startup of SqueezeCenter a bit, so you might get problems if you are running SqueezeCenter on slow hardware. (Boom, Transporter, Classic, Receiver, Controller, Radio, Touch, SoftSqueeze, SqueezePlay)</desc>
			<title lang="EN">Custom Browse</title>
		</plugin>
		<plugin name="CustomClockHelper" creator="Unsupported" email="" link="http://wiki.slimdevices.com/index.php/Custom_Clock_applet" maxTarget="*" minTarget="7.4.0" sha="3f0d6ea666b5d37e85899411ea65784f94b0021c" url="http://downloads.isaksson.info/download/do/downloadapplication?name=slimserver-customclockhelper&amp;filename=CustomClockHelper-2.11.94.zip" version="2.11.94">
			<changes lang="EN">- Available for free, no longer requires a license</changes>
			<desc lang="EN">This is a helper plugin for the Custom Clock screen saver applet, it makes it possible to create your own clock styles and modify the existing styles (Controller, Radio, Touch, SqueezePlay)</desc>
			<title lang="EN">Custom Clock Helper</title>
		</plugin>
		<plugin name="CustomScan" creator="Unsupported" email="" link="http://wiki.slimdevices.com/index.php/Custom_Scan_plugin" maxTarget="*" minTarget="7.4.0" sha="9eaca05d640f42d5843f54a8280c8e1a5e85eac6" url="http://downloads.isaksson.info/download/do/downloadapplication?name=slimserver-customscan&amp;filename=CustomScan-2.10.51.zip" version="2.10.51">
			<changes lang="EN">- Available for free, no longer requires a license
				- Compatible with LMS 7.9
			</changes>
			<desc lang="EN">Make it easier to develop modules that retreive additional information about artist, album, tracks from somehere. If used together with Custom Browse plugin, the included scanning modules for LastFM and custom tags makes it possible to browse music by LastFM tags or by a custom tag. (Boom, Transporter, Classic, Receiver, Controller, Radio, Touch, SoftSqueeze, SqueezePlay)</desc>
			<title lang="EN">Custom Scan</title>
		</plugin>
                <plugin name="CustomSkip" creator="Unsupported" email="" link="http://wiki.slimdevices.com/index.php/Custom_Skip_plugin" maxTarget="*" minTarget="7.4.0" sha="d78f922da552d56e7a0f04ae603de01b76e68d18" url="http://downloads.isaksson.info/download/do/downloadapplication?name=slimserver-customskip&amp;filename=CustomSkip-2.5.83.zip" version="2.5.83">
			<changes lang="EN">- Available for free, no longer requires a license</changes>
			<desc lang="EN">Makes it possible to skip tracks automatically in dynamic playlists. Makes it possible to skip tracks with low ratings, zapped tracks, short tracks and much more. (Boom, Transporter, Classic, Receiver, Radio, Touch, SoftSqueeze, SqueezePlay)</desc>
			<title lang="EN">Custom Skip</title>
                </plugin>
		<plugin name="DynamicPlayList" creator="Unsupported" email="" link="http://wiki.slimdevices.com/index.php/Dynamic_Playlist_plugin" maxTarget="*" minTarget="7.4.0" sha="0c8b9a0728a09dca35efe51e87a5a8f773236545" url="http://downloads.isaksson.info/download/do/downloadapplication?name=slimserver-dynamicplaylist&amp;filename=DynamicPlayList-2.10.247.zip" version="2.10.247">
			<changes lang="EN">- Available for free, no longer requires a license</changes>
			<desc lang="EN">Make it easy to create dynamic playlists for your own plugin. You simply need to implement two methods in your own plugin which returns the playlists and the next tracks. Currently at least supported by SQL Playlist plugin, TrackStat plugin, SugarCube plugin, iTunes Party Shuffle plugins and builtin support for saved static playlists. (Boom, Transporter, Classic, Receiver, Controller, Radio, Touch, SoftSqueeze, SqueezePlay)</desc>
			<title lang="EN">Dynamic Playlist</title>
		</plugin>
		<plugin name="MultiLibrary" creator="Unsupported" email="" link="http://wiki.slimdevices.com/index.php/Multi_Library_plugin" maxTarget="*" minTarget="7.4.0" sha="d3ba9b0c40ca7893719939a3703425736759ab2d" url="http://downloads.isaksson.info/download/do/downloadapplication?name=slimserver-multilibrary&amp;filename=MultiLibrary-2.8.168.zip" version="2.8.168">
			<changes lang="EN">- Available for free, no longer requires a license
				</changes>
			<desc lang="EN">Makes it possible to divide your SqueezeCenter library into different sub libraries, requires Custom Browse plugin to be able to browse the sub libraries. Please note that Multi Library needs a bit more resources than small plugins and might also slow down startup of SqueezeCenter a bit, so you might get problems if you are running SqueezeCenter on slow hardware. (Boom, Transporter, Classic, Receiver, Controller, Radio, Touch, SoftSqueeze, SqueezePlay)</desc>
			<title lang="EN">Multi Library</title>
		</plugin>
		<plugin name="SQLPlayList" creator="Unsupported" email="" link="http://wiki.slimdevices.com/index.php/SQL_Playlist_plugin" maxTarget="*" minTarget="7.4.0" sha="33b402200260f4111d37235484e5d54fdbec7ae8" url="http://downloads.isaksson.info/download/do/downloadapplication?name=slimserver-sqlplaylist&amp;filename=SQLPlayList-2.6.272.zip" version="2.6.272">
			<changes lang="EN">- Available for free, no longer requires a license
				- Compatible with LMS 7.9
			</changes>
			<desc lang="EN">Creates smart playlists based on SQL queries, its possible to create playlists similar to iTunes smart playlists if used together with ratings set with the TrackStat plugin. It requires Dynamic Playlist plugin. (Boom, Transporter, Classic, Receiver, Controller, Radio, Touch, SoftSqueeze, SqueezePlay)</desc>
			<title lang="EN">SQL Playlist</title>
		</plugin>
		<plugin name="TrackStat" creator="Unsupported" email="" link="http://wiki.slimdevices.com/index.php/TrackStat_plugin" maxTarget="*" minTarget="7.6.0" sha="4ea036c7853d540c01589be8de7755b515ab42e9" url="http://downloads.isaksson.info/download/do/downloadapplication?name=slimserver-trackstat&amp;filename=TrackStat-3.3.602.zip" version="3.3.602">
			<changes lang="EN">- Available for free, no longer requires a license</changes>
			<desc lang="EN">Store statistics such as rating, last played time and play counts so it survives a rescan and allows to to browse your library based on the statistic information. You can set the ratings via the Squeezebox player, CLI, Squeezebox Controller or web interface, ratings and statistic data can also be imported/exported from/to iTunes, Amarok and MusicIP Mixer. It also supports Dynamic Playlist plugin by adding dynamic playlists for all its statistics. Please note that TrackStat needs a bit more resources than small plugins and might also slow down startup of SqueezeCenter a bit, so you might get problems if you are running SqueezeCenter on slow hardware. (Boom, Transporter, Classic, Receiver, Controller, Radio, Touch, SoftSqueeze, SqueezePlay)</desc>
			<title lang="EN">TrackStat</title>
		</plugin>
	</plugins>
</extensions>
